原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
改编自《冰与火之歌》
原著 乔治·R·R·马丁
第六季 第一集
权力的游戏
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：草草 潇湘月影 欧沈娜
■
翻译：盐湖凉开水 妖精希亚 泰斯
校对：泰斯·雪诺 Silmar   顾问：屈畅(ccxx)
时间轴：泰斯·雪诺  Silmar
后期：吉吉·波顿  总监：泰斯·雪诺
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
是院子里传来的
It's coming from the courtyard.
是总司令大人
It's the Lord Commander!
叛徒
帮我把他抬进去
Help me get him inside.
是索恩干的
Thorne did this.
有多少兄弟你信得过
How many of your brothers do you think you can trust?
信得过
Trust?
就这屋里的人
The men in this room.
那狼认识你吗
Does the wolf know you?
我们需要一切帮助
We need all the help we can get.
戴佛斯爵士
Ser Davos.
我在火焰里看过他
I saw him in the flames
在临冬城作战
fighting at Winterfell.
火焰怎么样我不知道
I can't speak for the flames...
但他死了
but he's gone.
他是我们的总司令大人
He was our Lord Commander.
他就不该当上
He never should have been!
你们都知道你们为何而来
You all know why you're here.
琼恩·雪诺死了
Jon Snow is dead.
是谁杀了他
Who killed him?
是我
I did.
还有波文·马尔锡  奥赛尔·亚威克
And Bowen Marsh and Othell Yarwyck
还有本堡的其他将士
and the other officers in this castle.
-凶手  -叛徒
- Murderers! - Traitors!
没错
You're right!
我们都犯下了谋逆罪
We've committed treason, all of us.
琼恩·雪诺是我的总司令大人
Jon Snow was my Lord Commander.
我不喜欢他
I had no love for him.
这大家都知道
That was no secret.
但我从未违抗过命令
But I never once disobeyed an order.
忠诚是守夜人赖以存在的基石
Loyalty is the foundation on which the Night's Watch is built.
守夜人对我来说就是一切
And the Watch means everything to me.
我献出了我的生命
I have given my life,
我们都把生命交给了守夜人
we have all given our lives to the Night's Watch.
琼恩·雪诺要毁了守夜人
Jon Snow was going to destroy the Night's Watch.
他让野人进了我们的大门
He let the wildlings through our gates
从未有总司令大人这么做过
as no Lord Commander has ever done before.
他把野人曾劫掠  奸淫  烧杀的土地
He gave them the very land on which they reaved
给了他们
and raped and murdered.
雪诺总司令大人做了他认为正确的事
Lord Commander Snow did what he thought was right,
这我毫不怀疑
I've no doubt about that.
但他认为正确的事  会害死我们
And what he thought was right would have been the end of us.
他逼我们做一个万难的选择
He thrust a terrible choice upon us.
而我们做了
And we made it.
他肯定发现我们没去
He'll have seen we didn't come.
索恩这会儿应该已经宣布了
Thorne will have made it official by now.
黑城堡是他的了
Castle Black is his.
我才不管谁坐在高位上
I don't care who's sitting at the high table.
琼恩是我的朋友
Jon was my friend.
那些混蛋杀了他
And those fuckers butchered him.
我们以牙还牙
Now we return the favor.
我们是以寡敌众
We don't have the numbers.
-我们有冰原狼  -这不够
- We have a direwolf. - It's not enough.
我认识雪诺总司令大人的时间不长
I didn't know Lord Commander Snow for long,
但我相信
but I have to believe
他不希望自己的朋友无谓地死去
he wouldn't have wanted his friends to die for nothing.
如果你打算活到明天  你就不该待在这里
If you were planning to see tomorrow, you picked the wrong room.
我们今天都得死
We all die today.
要我说  我们尽量拉上索恩垫背
I say we do our best to take Thorne with us when we go.
我们是要抵抗  但不是非得死
We need to fight, but we don't need to die.
-只要有人帮忙  -谁会帮我们
- Not if we have help. - Who is gonna help us?
琼恩·雪诺救过的人不止你们几个
You're not the only ones who owe your lives to Jon Snow.
闩上门
Bolt the door.
别放人进来
Don't let anyone in.
我尽快回来
I'll be back as soon as I can.
我第一次见她时她才十一岁
She was 11 the first time I saw her.
驯兽长的女儿
The kennelmaster's daughter.
一身狗味儿
She smelled of dog.
我不比她大多少  但当时谁都怕我
I wasn't much older, but everybody was already afraid of me.
你就怕我
You certainly were.
可米兰达不怕
Myranda wasn't, though.
那些猎狗不能拿她怎样  我又能如何
What could I do to her that those hounds couldn't?
她天不怕地不怕
She was fearless.
没什么事是她干不出来的
There was nothing she wouldn't do.
你蒙受的痛苦将有人以千百倍的代价偿还
Your pain will be paid for a thousand times over.
真希望你能看到
I wish you could be here to watch.
要我给她挖坟吗  大人
Shall I have a grave dug for her, my lord?
还是派人搭火葬堆
Or would you rather the men build a pyre?
土埋  火葬
Buried, burned?
这是块好肉
This is good meat.
拿去喂猎犬
Feed it to the hounds.
你指挥骑兵很有一手
Your command of the cavalry was impressive.
多亏了你  伪王史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩死了
Thanks to you, the false king Stannis Baratheon is dead.
你知道是谁杀的吗
Do you know who struck the killing blow?
-不知道  -真遗憾
- No. - A shame.
我还想奖赏他呢
I'd reward the man.
不过  还是一场伟大的胜利
Still, a great victory.
你觉得自己胜利了吗
Do you feel like a victor?
我起兵造反
I rebelled against the crown
就为了让你迎娶珊莎·史塔克
to arrange your marriage to Sansa Stark.
你觉得趁夜偷袭  火烧马车
Do you think that burning wagons in the night
干掉疲倦不堪  寡不敌众的拜拉席恩
and mowing down tired, outnumbered Baratheons
能与迎战准备万全  兵强马壮的兰尼斯特相提并论吗
is the same as facing a prepared and provisioned Lannister army?
不能
No.
他们必将挥师讨伐
A reckoning will come.
我们需要北境的力量
We need the North to face it.
整个北境
The entire North.
没有珊莎·史塔克  北境不会支持我们
They won't back us without Sansa Stark.
然而珊莎·史塔克已经不在我们手上
We no longer have Sansa Stark.
你在她身上耍你那套把戏
You played your games with her.
在铁群岛的继承人身上耍你那套把戏
You played your games with the heir to the Iron Islands
现在他们都逃了
and now they're both gone.
我派了一队人马  带着最好的猎狗去抓他们
I have a team of men after them with some of my best hounds.
他们逃不远
They won't get far.
很好
I'm glad to hear it.
没有珊莎  你就生不出继承人
Without Sansa, you won't be able to produce an heir.
没有继承人
And without an heir, well...
但愿学士说得没错
let's hope the maesters are right
瓦妲夫人怀的是个男孩
and Lady Walda's carrying a boy.
不能停下
We can't stop.
我们必须过河
We have to cross here.
-我做不到  -只有这样才能甩掉猎犬
- I can't. - It's the only way to throw off the hounds.
太冷了  不行  我过不去  我会死的
But it's too cold. I can't. I won't make it. I'll die.
我见过他的猎犬怎么折磨人
I've seen what his hounds do to a person.
死也比被抓住强
This way is better.
这边  跟我来
Over here. Come on.
珊莎
Sansa.
叫它们闭嘴
Tell them to settle down!
别动  我去把他们引开
Stay here. I'll lure them away.
不  没有你  我逃不掉
No, I won't make it without you.
你可以的
You will.
往北走  一直往北
Go north, only north.
琼恩在黑城堡当总司令
Jon is Lord Commander at Castle Black.
他会帮助你
He'll help you.
看见人了吗
See somebody, eh?
-他们在那里  -抓住他们
- There they are! - Get them!
波顿夫人哪去了
Where is Lady Bolton?
-死了  -骗人
- Dead. - Liar.
她从城墙上跳下来时摔断了腿
She broke her leg jumping from the ramparts.
我留她在雪地里自生自灭
I left her to die in the snow.
找到了  快跑
Got something! Run!
拉住  别动
Resist. Stay.
别动
Stay.
我等不及想看这次拉姆斯会割下你哪个部位
I can't wait to see what parts Ramsay cuts off you this time.
有骑手
Rider!
-是谁  -是个贱女人
- Who is it? - It's a bloody woman.
不  饶命  不
No! Please! No!
珊莎小姐  我再次向您宣誓效忠
Lady Sansa, I offer my services once again.
我将保护您的安全  为您献计献策
I will shield your back and keep your counsel
危难之际愿奉献我的生命
and give my life for yours if need be.
我以新旧诸神之名起誓
I swear it by the old gods and the new.
我起誓
And I vow...
你将永远在我的壁炉边占有一席之地
that you shall always have a place by my hearth
你将...
and...
和我同桌喝酒  同餐吃肉
Meat and mead at my table.
meat and mead at my table.
我发誓永不令你
And I pledge to ask no service of you
行任何不义之事
that might bring you dishonor.
我以新旧诸神之名起誓
I swear it by the old gods and the new.
起来吧
Arise.
陛下  抱歉打扰您
Your Grace, I'm sorry to disturb you.
一艘多恩来的船驶进了港口
A ship from Dorne has sailed into the harbor.
弥赛菈
Myrcella.
你记得第一次见到死人吗
Do you remember the first time you saw a dead body?
母亲
Mother.
她死时我满脑子想着的
All I could think about when she died
就是她现在会怎样
was what would happen to her now.
每日每夜我都在想
Every day, every night,
妈妈现在是什么样子
what does Mama look like now?
她开始肿胀了吗
Has she started to bloat?
她的皮肤有没有变黑
Has her skin turned black?
她的嘴唇翻卷露出牙齿了吗
Have her lips peeled back from her teeth?
我想到弥赛菈被关在墓窖里
I think about locking Myrcella in a crypt.
我想到她美丽的面庞开始腐烂
I think about her beautiful little face starting to collapse.
别想了
Don't think about it.
我必须想
I have to.
我必须想  她不应该独自一人受苦
I have to. It's not right she has to suffer alone.
她已经解脱了  她走了
She's not suffering. She's gone.
没人能再伤害她
No one can hurt her anymore.
她那么善良
She was good.
从一出生就是那么甜美
From her first breath, she was so sweet.
我不知道她是从哪里来的
I don't know where she came from.
她完全不像我
She was nothing like me.
没有刻薄嫉妒  只有善良
No meanness, no jealousy, just good.
我知道
I know.
我以为  如果我能生出这样美好
I thought if I could make something so good,
这样纯洁的女儿
so pure...
-或许我就不是个怪物  -听我说
- Maybe I'm not a monster. - Listen-- listen to me.
她是我女儿  是我辜负了她
She was my daughter and I failed her.
不  我早知道会这样
No, I knew this would happen.
那女巫多年前就告诉我了
The witch told me years ago.
她预言我会有三个儿女  但他们都会死
She promised me three children and she promised me they'd die.
"以黄金为裹尸布"
"And gold their shrouds."
她说的一切都成了真
Everything she said came true.
你不可能阻止的
You couldn't have stopped it.
这是预言  是命运
It's prophecy. It's fate.
-你根本不信这话  -我当然相信
- You don't believe that. - Of course I do.
父亲死的那天  你对我说过
You told me yourself when Father died.
你说我们必须团结在一起
You said we had to stay together.
你说他们会将我们撕裂  夺去我们的一切
You said people would try to tear us apart, take what's ours.
那也是个预言
That was a prophecy, too.
我没听你的  你说的一切都成了真
I didn't listen to you and everything you said came true.
去他妈的预言  去他妈的命运
Fuck prophecy. Fuck fate.
除了我们  都他妈去死
Fuck everyone who isn't us.
唯一重要的只有我们
We're the only ones who matter,
世上唯一重要的就是我们
the only ones in this world.
他们从我们这里夺去的一切
And everything they've taken from us,
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
我们都加倍夺回来
we're going to take back and more.
我们要夺回一切
We're going to take everything there is.
七层地狱中挤满了圣洁之人的灵魂
"The Seven Hells brim with the souls of saintly men.
他们痛苦地嚎叫  他们的羞耻之强烈
They scream in agony and their shame is so great,
使他们连火焰也感觉不到
they do not feel the flames,
他们终于明白  若不是隐瞒了一桩罪行
for now they see if not for a single sin they concealed,
他们早已获得救赎
they were saved."
我想见我哥哥
I'd like to see my brother.
-忏悔  -求你了
- Confess. - Please.
他怎么样了  好歹告诉我一声
How is he? At least tell me that.
忏悔
Confess.
我是王后  我要求见我哥哥
I am the queen and I demand to see my brother.
罪人无权提要求
Sinners don't make demands.
他们只能忏悔
They make confessions.
乌尼亚修女
Septa Unella.
我们还有一位客人需要你
Our other guests need you.
没事了
There.
乌尼亚修女有时过于热心
Septa Unella can be overzealous at times.
我会跟她谈谈的
I'll speak with her.
我哥哥  能告诉我他怎样了吗
My brother, can you tell me how he is?
我并非为洛拉斯爵士而来
It isn't Ser Loras that brings me here.
你的丈夫非常想念你
Your husband misses you dearly.
夫妻之间的爱是神圣的
The love between a man and wife is sacred.
体现了诸神对世人的爱
It reflects the love the gods have for all of us.
然而罪孽使我们背离神圣
But sin leads us away from the sacred.
只有忏悔才能净化罪孽
And only confession can purge sin.
我没什么要忏悔的
I have nothing to confess.
那么你相信自己是纯洁的
So you believe you are pure?
完美的
Perfect?
无可指摘
Wholly without sin?
谁也做不到
None of us are.
你已经上路了
You have started down the path.
但还有很长的路要走
But you have many miles to go.
我一直很嫉妒奥柏伦
I always envied Oberyn.
他活过
He lived.
真真正正地活过
He truly lived.
游历世界
Sailed around the world.
与各国的勇士战斗
Fought men from every country.
睡过世界上最漂亮的女人
Lay with the most beautiful women alive.
-和男人  -对  还有男人
- And men. - And men.
他什么都经历过
He experienced everything
而我只能坐在这里
while I sat here in Dorne
为多恩的子民安居乐业而竭尽心力
trying my best to keep my people alive and well fed.
但这就是生活
But that is life.
每个人都有自己的角色
We each have our roles.
奥柏伦生来就是冒险家
Oberyn was born to be an adventurer.
而我生来就是统治者
And I was born to rule.
诸神不是傻瓜
The gods are not fools.
你会是个差劲的冒险家
You would have been a lousy adventurer.
至于奥柏伦
And Oberyn, pfft,
他一定是个糟糕的统治者
he would have been a terrible ruler.
你知道吗  你母亲是个充满智慧的女人
Your mother is a brilliant woman, you know that?
道朗亲王
Prince Doran.
弥赛菈公主
The Princess Myrcella.
你上次出宫是什么时候
When was the last time you left this palace?
你太不了解你的子民
You don't know your own people.
不知道他们对你的厌恶
Their disgust for you.
伊莉亚·马泰尔被奸杀  你什么都没做
Elia Martell raped and murdered, and you did nothing.
奥柏伦·马泰尔惨遭屠戮  你还是无动于衷
Oberyn Martell butchered, and you did nothing.
你不配做多恩人
You're not a Dornishman.
你不配做我们的亲王
You're not our prince.
我的儿子崔斯丹
My son Trystane...
你的儿子跟你一样软弱
Your son is weak just like you.
多恩再也不会被软弱的人统治了
And weak men will never rule Dorne again.
我说过我不饿
I told you I'm not hungry.
我们不是来给你送食物的
We're not here to feed you.
我们是来取你小命的
We're here to kill you.
你想死在谁手上  她还是我
You want her to do it or me?
我们是一家人  我不想伤害你们
We are family. I don't want to hurt you.
她还是我
Her or me?
你
You.
很好
Good.
聪明小子
Smart boy.
你是个贪婪的小婊子  知道吗
You're a greedy bitch, you know that?
我们要想解决这座城市的问题
We're never going to fix what's wrong with this city
坐在八百呎高的金字塔上可不行
from the top of an 800-foot pyramid.
不会有事的
We'll be fine.
我们的打扮跟普通商人没什么两样
We're dressed like common merchants.
你走起路来像个富人
You walk like a rich person.
你花了不少精力研究富人走路的样子吗
You've spent a lot of time studying the way rich people walk?
你走起路来就好像这石板路是你自家的一样
You walk as though the paving stones were your personal property.
我还是小男孩的时候专门偷你这种人
I used to steal from people like you when I was a boy.
幸好你已经不是小男孩了
It's a good thing you're not a boy anymore.
因为你没有命根子
Because you have no cock.
给你小孩的
买吃的
吃的
她以为你要吃了她的孩子
She thinks you want to eat her baby.
他不太会说瓦雷利亚语
他只是想给你点钱
让你给孩子买些吃的
杀死伟主  弥莎也是伟主
-在瓦雷利亚语里  弥莎就是母亲  -我知道
- Mhysa means mother in Valyrian. - I know what mhysa means.
-是谁写的呢  -这可说不准
- Who wrote it? - Hard to know.
我们的女王在弥林可没有以前那么受欢迎了
Our queen is not as popular in Meereen as she used to be.
是鹰身女妖之子干的
The Sons of the Harpy?
很有可能
Very possibly.
丹妮莉丝·坦格利安夺走了他们最珍贵的财产
Daenerys Targaryen took away their most valuable property,
还告诉他们人本来就不是财产
told them human beings weren't even property to begin with.
你应该明白他们为什么不开心吧
You can see why they're unhappy.
当然
Of course,
也有可能是自由人干的
it could also be the freed men.
因为长夜黑暗  处处险恶
光之王派龙之母来拯救你们
那些心向黑暗的人却赶走了她
许多曾经的奴隶觉得丹妮莉丝把他们抛弃了
Many of the former slaves feel that Daenerys has abandoned them.
她的确驾龙高飞  没有回来
She did fly away on a dragon and not come back.
你们要怎样回应
你们是紧握双手等待龙之母的归来
还是接过她的火炬
没有丹妮莉丝女王  你们会为自我救赎而战吗
这是个难题
It's a problem.
恐惧导致弥林停滞不前
Fear has brought Meereen to a standstill.
不管你是谁  不管你去哪
Whoever you are, wherever you go,
城里总有人想置你于死地
someone in this city wants to murder you.
我们连敌人是谁都不知道  谈何战斗
We can't fight an enemy we don't know.
鹰身女妖之子在竞技场发动的袭击
The Sons of the Harpy planned their attack
可谓深思熟虑
in the fighting pits very carefully,
说明他们背后有人操纵
which means they take orders from someone.
你开始着手找这个人了吗
And have you started looking for that someone?
我的小小鸟已经飞上天了
My little birds have already taken wing.
它们很快就会唱着黄金面具的歌儿飞回来
Soon they'll return, singing songs of men in gold masks.
看来我们暂时去不成维斯特洛了
Well, we won't be sailing to Westeros anytime soon.
山羊吗
Goat?
公羊
Ram.
你认为是咱们的朋友干的
You think our friend got him?
不知道除了它还有谁能融化公羊的角
Don't know anything else that can melt a ram's horn.
这么说我们走对了路
We're on the right path, then.
也许她心生倦意了
Perhaps she's tired of being queen.
我认为她不太喜欢当女王
I don't think she likes it very much.
她那么聪明  当然不喜欢
She's too smart to like it.
说不定她飞到别处去了
Maybe she's flown somewhere else,
离我们这种人远远的
somewhere far away from men like us.
我去过很多地方
I've been all over the world.
没见过我们这样的逃亡者
There's no escaping men like us.
不想从她身边逃走吧
There's no escaping her, eh?
走了又回来  为什么
You keep coming back. Why?
你知道为什么
You know why.
很痛苦吧
Isn't it frustrating
爱上一个对你毫无感觉的人
wanting someone who doesn't want you back?
当然
Of course it is.
你真是浪漫  我佩服你
You're a romantic. I admire that.
有时看着你  我就会想
Sometimes I look at you and I think,
我老了以后也是这样吧
"So that's what I'll be like when I grow old."
只要你能活到老
If you grow old.
只要我能活到老
If I grow old.
但愿吧
I hope I do.
我想亲眼看看
I want to see what the world looks like
被她征服的世界
when she's done conquering it.
我也想
So do I.
军队吗
Huh, an army?
不是军队
Not an army.
是部落
A horde.
多斯拉克人
Dothraki?
他们把她抓走了
They have her.
她可能见过鬼魂
我朋友的母亲见过鬼魂  然后头发变白了
粉人害怕太阳
皮肤会被灼伤
她在太阳底下站了太久  头发就变白了
你说她的阴毛是白的吗
你干过白阴毛的女孩吗
就干过你奶奶一个
我会请求摩洛卡奥把你送给我睡一晚
你觉得怎么样
眼睛很美  但人太傻
撅着屁股又不用动脑筋
我干完了喜欢说话  否则跟狗没什么两样
不
No.
献给你  我的卡奥
在丘陵里找到的白发女孩
看看她的嘴唇  吾血之血
蓝眼女人都是女巫
大家都知道
砍了她的头  别叫她给你施了咒语
就算我眼瞎了
一听到我的老婆们说
砍了她的头
我就知道这女人一定很美
好在我没有瞎
第一次看漂亮女人的裸体
还有更美妙的事情吗
杀死另一个卡奥
没错  杀死另一个卡奥
占领一座城池  奴役城里的人
把他们的神像带回维斯·多斯拉克
驯服一匹野马
迫使它服从你的旨意
第一次看漂亮女人的裸体是最美妙的五件事之一
别碰我
我乃坦格利安家族的风暴降生丹妮莉丝
不焚者
弥林女王
安达尔  洛伊拿人和先民的女王
草海上的卡丽熙
解放者  龙之母
你是无名之人  蝼蚁之辈
虚无国度的卡丽熙
你是摩洛卡奥的奴隶
今晚我会睡你
如果伟大骏马开恩
你会给我生个儿子
懂了吗
我不会跟你睡
也不会给你和任何人生孩子
除非太阳从西边升起  在东边落下
我就说她是女巫
砍了她的头
我喜欢她  勇气可嘉
我是卓戈卡奥的妻子  他是拔尔勃卡奥之子
卓戈卡奥死了
我知道
我烧掉了他的遗体
原谅我  我不知道
卡奥的寡妻是不能睡的
不会有人碰你
我保证
如果你们护送我回弥林
我会送你的卡拉萨一千良马  以表谢意
卡奥死了
卡丽熙只有一个去处
维斯·多斯拉克  多希卡林的归宿
与诸多卡奥的寡妻们共度余生
大家都知道
不管什么都是有价钱的
But there has to be a price to pay for everything.
我知道  可你有没有告诉过他
I know, but have you tried telling him that?
谢谢
Thank you.
那个御林铁卫出了事  谁还敢去
Who'd go there after what happened to that Kingsguard?
-说不定是他自己惹事  -也许是的
- Probably had it coming. - Maybe so,
但我不想冒险
but I'm not risking it.
-办不到  -好吧
- Just can't do it. - All right.
而且实诚  他人不错
Honesty as well. He gets it.
你在听吗  盲眼女孩
Are you listening, blind girl?
听到他们的话了吗
Do you hear them talking?
有人对你说话吗
Do any of them talk to you?
没有
No.
真可怜
So sad.
起来  来打  盲眼女孩
Stand and fight, blind girl.
我看不见
I can't see.
这是你的问题  不是我的
That's your problem, not mine.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
戴佛斯爵士  我们没道理开战
Ser Davos, we have no cause to fight.
你我都是抹过圣油的骑士
We are both anointed knights.
听见了吗  小子们  不用害怕
Hear that, lads? Nothing to fear.
我会赦免所有兄弟
I will grant amnesty to all brothers
只要天黑前放下武器
who throw down their arms before nightfall.
至于你  戴佛斯爵士  我放你南下
And you, Ser Davos, I will allow you to travel south
还你自由  还送你一匹好马
a free man with a fresh horse.
还要羊肉
And some mutton.
我要一些羊肉
I'd like some mutton.
-什么  -我不大会打猎
- What? - I'm not much of a hunter.
我需要一些吃的  不然南下途中会饿肚子
I'll need some food if I'm gonna make it south without starving.
我们给你吃的
We'll give you food.
你愿意的话也可以带上红袍女
You can bring the Red Woman with you if you like.
或者留给我们  随你便
Or you can leave her here with us, whichever you choose.
但是天黑前必须投降  否则只能见血了
But surrender by nightfall or this ends with blood.
谢谢你  艾里沙爵士
Thank you, Ser Alliser.
我们商量一下
We'll discuss amongst ourselves
再给你答复
and come back to you with an answer.
小子们  我一辈子都在避免和那种人打交道
Boys, I've been running from men like that all my life.
以我的阅历  只要我们打开门...
In my learned opinion, we open that door--
他们就会把我们赶尽杀绝
And they'll slaughter us all.
他们想进来  他们也进得来
They want to come in, they're gonna come in.
是  但我们不需要替他们省力气
Aye, but we don't need to make it easy for them.
艾迪是我们唯一的机会
Edd is our only chance.
真他妈的可怜  忧郁的艾迪是我们唯一的机会
It's a sad fucking statement if Dolorous Edd is our only chance.
还有红袍女
There's always the Red Woman.
一个红头发怎么对付四十个全副武装的汉子
What's one redhead gonna do against 40 armed men?
你没见过她的能耐  我可见过
You haven't seen her do what I've seen her do.
■
人人影视字幕组
历时一年打造的一款基于影视例句的英语
学习软件由于开发资金庞大希望众筹来筹
够资金希望得到大家的支持!
微博：http://weibo.com/yyets
微博：http://weibo.com/rrcd
人人词典项目众筹召集
网站：http://www.91dict.com
邮箱：fanyi@yyets.com